{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"97.5/6.5",
			"answer":"97.5/6.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.912/0.081",
			"answer":"0.912/0.081",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.56/0.57",
			"answer":"7.56/0.57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"98.7/6.3",
			"answer":"98.7/6.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"16.2/0.21",
			"answer":"16.2/0.21",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.71/1.1",
			"answer":"6.71/1.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.485/0.97",
			"answer":"0.485/0.97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"49.5/5.5",
			"answer":"49.5/5.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.81/0.71",
			"answer":"7.81/0.71",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.506/4.6",
			"answer":"0.506/4.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}